Lish mss., 1951-2017 LMC 2404
Lilly Library
- II. Writings
  - By Other Authors
    - Petroski - Reinbold (Box 69)
      - Redel, Victoria, (2 folders) (Box 69)
        - Stories (Box 69)
          - Am I Hot? Am I Cold? (Box 69)
          - Breaking the Air (Box 69)
          - He's Back (Box 69)
          - Porch Light (Box 69)
          - Soul to Take (Box 69)
          - We Were Russia So It Said (Box 69)
        - Loverboy (Box 69)
      - Reed, John (Box 69)
        - First Hour (Box 69)
      - Reg, Gustus (Box 69)
        - Kidding (Box 69)
        - The Psoriasis Diet (Box 69)
        - Two Families (Box 69)
        - What Is Left to Link Us (Box 69)
        - Weight (Box 69)
      - Reid, Elwood (Box 69)
        - Lime [aka Ugly] (Box 69)
      - Reinbold, James S., (3 folders) (Box 69)
        - Stories (Box 69)
          - The End of diLonghi Hermit (Box 69)
          - A Family Portrait (Box 69)
          - Houses (Box 69)
          - Two Short Stories and a Novella (Box 69)
          - Ventriloquism, or: The Trunk (Box 69)
        - Cartography (Box 69)
        - Eels (Box 69)
    - Reinbold (end) - Roberts (Box 70)
      - Reinbold, James S. (end), (2 folders) (Box 70)
        - In the Oasis Room (Box 70)
        - Moving [aka Mr. Staal] (Box 70)
      - Reingold, Jacquelyn (Box 70)
        - The Men Who Wanted to Be President (Box 70)
        - Three Words (Box 70)
      - Renner, B. (Box 70)
        - Container vs. Contained: An elimae Forum (Box 70)
      - Renner, Cooper S. [aka Cooper Esteban] (Box 70)
        - Achilles on Lefki (Box 70)
        - After He Found Out (Box 70)
        - After Hearing on CNN that Women in India Are Aborting Daughters (Box 70)
        - Ares' Epitaph: or, Christentum Ueber Alles (Box 70)
        - Avernus (Box 70)
        - Baseball Lyric (Box 70)
        - Callisthenes on How Alexander Came to the Throne (Box 70)
        - Casanova (Box 70)
        - Chrism (Box 70)
        - Coyotes (Box 70)
        - EC(H)O (Box 70)
        - Eleven (Box 70)
        - Extrapolation (Box 70)
        - For V*KR*M S*TH (Box 70)
        - Form Triumphs of Over Function: or, the Dilemma of Consciousness (Box 70)
        - From a Levee Overlooking the Trinity (Box 70)
        - Hanging Out at the Parthenon; or, A Poem in the Manner of Mary Jo; or, In Celebration of the Latest Winner of the Amy Lowell Poetry Traveling Scholarship; or, Where Is Mean Old Uncle Ezra When You Really Need Him? (Box 70)
        - Industrial Avenue (Box 70)
        - Inside Eden (Box 70)
        - Lawrence (Box 70)
        - Mary's Lover (Box 70)
        - The Maze Bull (Box 70)
        - Mujerados (Box 70)
        - Origami (Box 70)
        - Parthenogenitor (Box 70)
        - Poem (Box 70)
        - Recapitulation (Box 70)
        - Southwestern Poem; or, No Roof but Lack of Imagination and a Deadly Dull Earnestness (Box 70)
        - Sufi Gunfighter Starring Rumi Bly as Six Gun Kabir (Box 70)
        - That Day (Box 70)
        - Theodicy (Box 70)
        - Under Vespian (Box 70)
        - Untitled (Box 70)
        - Yaakov Ben Nirriti (Box 70)
        - Warhol Enters Heaven (Box 70)
        - We Are Seven (Box 70)
      - Rennie, Doug (Box 70)
        - Boxes (Box 70)
        - The List (Box 70)
      - Rhoton, Laura (Box 70)
        - The End of the This [aka Omnibus] (Box 70)
        - The Mine (Box 70)
      - Ricchiute, David (Box 70)
        - My Unspeakable Secret (Box 70)
      - Rice, Jackson (Box 70)
        - The Day They Cured Boredom Plot Summery (Box 70)
      - Rice, Oliver (Box 70)
        - An American in Santa Fe (Box 70)
        - Aspects of the Novel (Box 70)
        - On the Explication of Maps (Box 70)
      - Richard, Mark, (6 folders) (Box 70)
        - Stories, (2 folders) (Box 70)
          - Fishboy (Box 70)
          - Friendship [aka Charity] (Box 70)
          - Genius (Box 70)
          - Just Name Someplace (Box 70)
          - Little Firebugs, Little Lightening Flies (Box 70)
          - The Louisiana Purchase [aka All God's Money] (Box 70)
          - Merry Christmas, Michael Christian (Box 70)
          - Never in this World (Box 70)
          - People Don't Write Letters Like They Used To (Box 70)
          - Plymouth Rock (Box 70)
          - Strays (Box 70)
          - Surrender (Box 70)
          - The Theory of Man (Box 70)
          - This Is Us, Excellent (Box 70)
          - Where Blue Is Blue (Box 70)
        - Fishboy Copy 1, (2 folders) (Box 70)
        - Fishboy Copy 2, (2 folders) (Box 70)
        - Fishboy Proof (Box 70)
        - The Ice at the Bottom of the World Author's Proof (Box 70)
        - The Ice at the Bottom of the World Blue Pages (Box 70)
        - The Ice at the Bottom of the World Pages, (2 folders) (Box 70)
      - Richards, Peter (Box 70)
        - Bulrushes (Box 70)
        - The Drift (Box 70)
        - Endangering (Box 70)
        - Going Down (Box 70)
        - The Security Council (Box 70)
      - Richey, James (Box 70)
        - The Yellow Circle (Box 70)
      - Richman, Elliot (Box 70)
        - Still Life with Hanging Man (Box 70)
      - Rickstad, Eric (Box 70)
        - The Blue Car [aka A Classic] (Box 70)
      - Rima, Larry (Box 70)
        - An Interview with Richard Stern (Box 70)
      - Ringer, R.C. (Box 70)
        - The Sitter [aka A Place to Go] (Box 70)
        - Things Happen (Box 70)
        - Visiting (Box 70)
      - Robbins, James (Box 70)
        - Leper (Box 70)
      - Roberts, Charles Stewart (Box 70)
        - The Undiscovered Country (Box 70)
          - Modigliani, Italian Painter in France (Box 70)
          - Reading USA Today [aka Sarajevo (Box 70)
          - Letter to Oxford, Georgia (Box 70)
          - Homage to Isabella (Box 70)
          - The Deerskin (Box 70)
          - Four Suicides (Box 70)
          - Christmas Eve (Box 70)
          - The Fatalist (Box 70)
          - Studies in Composure (Box 70)
          - Pastel Colors (Box 70)
          - A Morning Letter (Box 70)
          - A Departure (Box 70)
          - Four Rose Themes (Box 70)
          - Waiting Room (Box 70)
          - Vida (Box 70)
          - The First Night (Box 70)
          - Bayreuth (Box 70)
          - James Joyce (Box 70)
          - Hart Crane (Box 70)
          - The Death of Delmore (Box 70)
          - Ezra Pound (Box 70)
          - The Young Poet (Box 70)
          - Quincy Square (Box 70)
          - Sound and Fury (Box 70)
          - St. Louis Woman (Box 70)
          - Chapel Hill Living Room (Box 70)
          - Dinner with My Father and His Friend (Box 70)
          - Cezanne (Box 70)
          - Letter from Arles (Box 70)
          - Vuillard (Box 70)
          - Gauguin in Tahiti (Box 70)
          - Variations on Gauguin (Box 70)
          - Kandinsky's Moscow in the Early Morning (Box 70)
          - Vermeer's Head of a Girl (Box 70)
          - The Unfinished Tenth Symphony (Box 70)
          - Marcus Aurelius (Box 70)
          - Kierkegaard (Box 70)
          - The Postcard (Box 70)
          - Flaubert (Box 70)
          - Days of Angel, Days of Prayer (Box 70)
          - Pasternak (Box 70)
          - Marina Tsvetayeva (Box 70)
          - Rainer Maria Rilke (Box 70)
          - Marbot (Box 70)
          - Wordsworth (Box 70)
          - The Birds of Chelsea (Box 70)
          - Disraeli of England (Box 70)
          - Carlyle (Box 70)
          - T.S. Eliot of London (Box 70)
          - Raleigh (Box 70)
          - Napoleon in Russia (Anno 1812) (Box 70)
          - Lord Nelson (Box 70)
          - Lord Cornwallis (Box 70)
          - Francis Marion (Box 70)
          - Banastre Tarleton (Box 70)
          - George Washington (Box 70)
          - Jefferson at Monticello (Box 70)
          - Adams of Quincy (Box 70)
          - Frederick Douglass (Box 70)
          - Andersonville (Box 70)
          - Lincoln (Box 70)
          - Prisoner After War (Box 70)
          - Sidney Lanier (Box 70)
          - Between the Levee and the River (Box 70)
          - Grief or Nothing (Box 70)
          - Cassone (Box 70)
          - Paris in August (Box 70)
          - Six Letters to a Son (Box 70)
          - The Dusty Chandelier (Box 70)
          - Note to Grandmother Roberts (Box 70)
          - Leaving Atlanta (Box 70)
          - The Photographer (Box 70)
          - Postscript (Box 70)
          - Alla Prima (Box 70)
          - Yeates (Box 70)
          - Husband and Wife (Box 70)
          - The Storm (Box 70)
          - A First Bereavement (Box 70)
          - The Day I Signed Seperation Papers (Box 70)
          - The Children (Box 70)
          - The New Year (Box 70)
          - Rainbow Café (Box 70)
          - Fatherhood (Box 70)
          - Separation (Box 70)
          - Man of War (Box 70)
          - Evening Under Lamplight (Box 70)
          - Canteloupe from Canteloupa (Box 70)
          - Winter (Box 70)
          - Chelsea (Box 70)
          - Onslow Gardens (Box 70)
          - London Pub (Box 70)
          - London (Box 70)
          - Decatur Cemetary (Box 70)
          - Reading Faulkner (Box 70)
          - After Edgar Allen Poe (Box 70)
          - A Remembrance of My Mother (Box 70)
    - Robinson - Robison (Box 71)
      - Robinson, Lou (Box 71)
        - The Tendency and Flair (Box 71)
      - Robison, Mary (Box 71)
        - Stories, (4 folders) (Box 71)
          - An Amateurs Guide to the Night (Box 71)
          - Apostasy (Box 71)
          - Beach Traffic (Box 71)
          - Beatniks (Box 71)
          - Camilla's Different Clothes (Box 71)
          - Coach (Box 71)
          - A Common Spring (Box 71)
          - Cryptography or The Last Message of Mr. Moto (Box 71)
          - The Dictionary in the Laundry Chute [aka When It Rains] (Box 71)
          - Falling Away (Box 71)
          - Felt Pieces (Box 71)
          - Grace (Box 71)
          - Heart (Box 71)
          - In Jewel (Box 71)
          - Kite and Paint (Box 71)
          - Look at Me Go [aka Lighthouse Point] (Box 71)
          - Looking at the Orange Faces [aka Yours] (Box 71)
          - May Queen (Box 71)
          - The Nature of Almost Anything [aka Turn Off the Radio] (Box 71)
          - Nothing's It (Box 71)
          - Orange (Box 71)
          - Pretty Ice (Box 71)
          - Sisters (Box 71)
          - Smart (Box 71)
          - Smoke (Box 71)
          - Snow (Box 71)
          - Stay with Me (Box 71)
          - Sunday, Late (Box 71)
          - You Know Charles (Box 71)
        - An Amateur's Guide to the Night Master Set, (2 folders) (Box 71)
        - An Amateur's Guide to the Night Master Set, (2 folders) (Box 71)
        - An Amateur's Guide to the Night Printer's ms. (Box 71)
        - An Amateur's Guide to the Night Master Set, (2 folders) (Box 71)
        - The Short Fictions of Mary Robison [eventually retitled Book of Days then Days] (Box 71)
        - Book of Days [eventually retitled Days] (Box 71)
        - Book of Days First Proofs (Box 71)
        - Book of Days Proofreading Master Proofs (Box 71)
        - Book of Days Master Page Proofs (Box 71)
        - Days Repro Pages, (3 folders) (Box 71)
    - Robison - Rooke (Box 72)
      - Robison, Mary (end) (Box 72)
        - Days Blues (Box 72)
        - Oh! Galleys (Box 72)
        - Something Nice and Something New Copy 1 [aka This Way], (3 folders) (Box 72)
        - Something Nice and Something New Copy 2, (3 folders) (Box 72)
      - Rodriguez, Jesús Ramón (Box 72)
        - Stories, (2 folders) (Box 72)
          - Anselle's Ribbon (Box 72)
          - Being Around [aka The Night That People Are Not Good For Burning] (Box 72)
          - The Boys in the Highland (Box 72)
          - Eating the Father's Penis, an Esssay for Leonard Michaels (Box 72)
          - The Greatest Story Ever Told [aka A Man Has Needs] (Box 72)
          - Heroin (Box 72)
          - The New Century (Box 72)
          - The Rapture Within These Walls (Box 72)
          - Sink [aka A Messed Up World] (Box 72)
          - Story for a Child Born Dead (Box 72)
          - Unravelling (Box 72)
          - Where We Live (Box 72)
        - Corn-whiskey Edged Penitence to the Heartland (?), (2 folders) (Box 72)
          - The Night People Are Not Good For Burning (Box 72)
          - Soil (Box 72)
          - Unravelling (Box 72)
          - The New Century (Box 72)
          - The Dragonslayer (Box 72)
          - Bendición (Box 72)
          - Standing (Box 72)
          - The Mexican Gun (Box 72)
          - Thoughts of Heaven (Box 72)
          - Anselle's Ribbon (Box 72)
          - In Nevada, Drving, the Remarkable Thing (Box 72)
          - Manhattan (Box 72)
          - What It Is You Feel at Times Like This (Box 72)
          - The Killing Place (Box 72)
          - The Boys in the Highlands (Box 72)
          - The Rapture, Within These Walls (Box 72)
          - Touching Jesus (Box 72)
          - Fishing the Silver Sky (Box 72)
      - Rodriguez, Richard (Box 72)
        - Days of Obligation (Box 72)
      - Roe, Christopher (Box 72)
        - [As I threw the rocks…] (Box 72)
        - [Christopher: What happens…] (Box 72)
        - A Close Look at Myself (Box 72)
        - The Crescent Moon (Box 72)
        - [Getting form here to there…] (Box 72)
        - [The greenest pastures…] (Box 72)
        - [People are wonderful…] (Box 72)
        - Petros and the Vase of Happiness (Box 72)
        - Raja Rao (Box 72)
        - Shakespeare and the King (Box 72)
        - Stargazer (Box 72)
        - Suicide Passion (Box 72)
        - [The thought of being lonely…] (Box 72)
        - Truly (Box 72)
      - Rogers (Box 72)
        - Crazy Times (Box 72)
      - Rogers, Bruce Holland (Box 72)
        - Murder, Mystery (Box 72)
      - Rogers, George (Box 72)
        - Living Near Canada (Box 72)
      - Rogers, Michael (Box 72)
        - Don't Worry About the Bear (Box 72)
      - Romm, Jamie (Box 72)
        - The Galvanization of Lenny Lottovich (Box 72)
      - Rooke, Leon (Box 72)
        - Stories (Box 72)
          - Art (Box 72)
          - Breasts [aka Foot in Field Story] (Box 72)
          - Drivers [aka No Pears] (Box 72)
          - Show People (Box 72)
          - Swami (Box 72)
        - The Book of Fate, or the Biogrphy of Nancy Sullivan (Box 72)
        - Fat Woman, (3 folders) (Box 72)
    - Rooke (end) - Schutt, Christine (Box 73)
      - Rooke, Leon (end) (Box 73)
        - A Good Baby, (3 folders) (Box 73)
        - Shakespeare's Dog Draft 1 (Box 73)
        - Shakespeare's Dog Draft 2, (2 folders) (Box 73)
      - Rosenberg, David (Box 73)
        - The Eden Revelation (Box 73)
        - Losing One's Place (Box 73)
        - TV of Sun (Box 73)
      - Rosenberg, Harold (Box 73)
        - Art Critic, New Yorker (Box 73)
        - Dr. James Watson (Box 73)
      - Rosenberg, Liz (Box 73)
        - Things (Box 73)
      - Roth, Philip (Box 73)
        - [Interview] (Box 73)
      - Rowe, Alick (Box 73)
        - The Dogs (Box 73)
      - Ryan, David (Box 73)
        - The Beekeeper (Box 73)
        - Blush (Box 73)
      - Ryan, R.M. (Box 73)
        - Ars Poetica Rule One (Box 73)
        - Beckett (Box 73)
        - The Figure the Fugue Makes (Box 73)
      - Rybicki, John, (3 folders) (Box 73)
        - Writings (Box 73)
          - After The Last of the Mohicans (Box 73)
          - [Archer…] (Box 73)
          - Back Home (Box 73)
          - The Beast Traveling Back to its Hole (Box 73)
          - Before the Reading, at a Philip's 66 (Box 73)
          - The Blown Up Goat (Box 73)
          - [Brave Youth…] (Box 73)
          - Brothers (Box 73)
          - The Children's Home (Box 73)
          - Cliff Notes (Box 73)
          - [Dear Helena…] (Box 73)
          - Delton Writer Opens home for Workshop Sessions [article] (Box 73)
          - Driving Through It (Box 73)
          - Ed Mullen, Hooker - Detroit Tradesman Rugby Football Club (Box 73)
          - Fire Psalm (Box 73)
          - Flying (Box 73)
          - The Green Side of Town (Box 73)
          - I Am Mad and This Is How I Am (Box 73)
          - [I train my train into this city…] (Box 73)
          - In the Can After Work, Letter to Hutch (Box 73)
          - Inside the Dog (Box 73)
          - Jeptha Lake (Box 73)
          - Junkyard Poem (Box 73)
          - The Left Side of the Flesh (Box 73)
          - Letter to Bob Hicok (Box 73)
          - Letter to Russell Edson (Box 73)
          - [Matt, Even when the wide earth…] (Box 73)
          - [Matt, Got halfbacks ripping…] (Box 73)
          - Poem on the Back of an Envelope (Box 73)
          - The Postman's Rivers (Box 73)
          - The Reading (Box 73)
          - Satellite to that Last Kiss (Box 73)
          - Scene Eleven (Box 73)
          - [She remembers, as a little girl…] (Box 73)
          - Slogans (Box 73)
          - Snow (Box 73)
          - Sparta Rodeo (Box 73)
          - St. Claire of Montefalco (Box 73)
          - Stained Glass Johnny (Box 73)
          - Subterranean (Box 73)
          - Sweet Star Chisel, Dearest Flaming Crumbs in Your Beard Lord (Box 73)
          - This Sun (Box 73)
          - Trumpeter Swans (Box 73)
          - The Twin-headed Beast (Box 73)
          - Untitled (Box 73)
          - [When the cancer's zapped and gone…] (Box 73)
          - [You gut the air…] (Box 73)
        - Dancing the Cancer Down to Dust (Box 73)
        - Poetry Collections (Box 73)
          - Traveling at High Speeds (Box 73)
            - Slogans (Box 73)
            - T.H. Hickory - Trial Guernsey Sire On the Breeders Exchange (Box 73)
            - Finding Miss Right (Box 73)
            - Carnival (Box 73)
            - Driving Through It (Box 73)
            - Metaphor on a Roadside Kill (Box 73)
            - Testimony After Sleep (Box 73)
            - On the Possible Conception of My First Child (Box 73)
            - Tuning the Morning (Box 73)
            - Tuesday Morning (Box 73)
            - Holocaust Seen from the Moon (Box 73)
            - Rolling with It, Kansas (Box 73)
            - I Am Mad and This Is How I Am (Box 73)
            - Cleaning the Auger (Box 73)
            - View from a Farmhouse Window (Box 73)
            - Billy Martin Speaks to His Team (Box 73)
            - Walking Home (Box 73)
            - At Alfred A. Knopf (Box 73)
            - Coal Boys (Box 73)
            - While She Sleeps (Box 73)
            - Traveling at High Speeds (Box 73)
            - July 29th (Box 73)
            - Walnut Manor Dairy Farm (Box 73)
            - The Edge of a Round World (Box 73)
            - Ringing In (Box 73)
            - Killers (Box 73)
            - First Storm, Day Off Work (Box 73)
            - Premarriage DT's (Box 73)
            - Tearing Down the Uniroyal Plant - Detroit Michigan (Box 73)
            - After 'The Star Spangled Banner' (Box 73)
            - 6:00 A.M. (Box 73)
            - Brother Ben (Box 73)
            - The Impossible Borders of Permanence (Box 73)
            - Everywhere (Box 73)
            - Making Tracks (Box 73)
            - St. Jude's Home for Delinquent Boys (Box 73)
            - The Hands of Absence (Box 73)
          - Untitled collection (Box 73)
            - Tuesday Morning (Box 73)
            - Walking Home (Box 73)
            - Tuning the Morning (Box 73)
            - T.H. Hickory - Trial Guernsey Sire On the Breeders Exchange (Box 73)
            - Cleaning the Auger, Wet Corn Silo (Box 73)
            - Testimony After Sleep (Box 73)
      - Ryder (Box 73)
        - [Hole up on that settee so long…] (Box 73)
      - Ryder, Pamela (Box 73)
        - Ark (Box 73)
        - Sirens, Siren (Box 73)
        - Three Men (Box 73)
        - Untitled (Box 73)
      - Sachs, Sheldon (Box 73)
        - Flannery O'Connor/A Circle in the Fire (Box 73)
      - Sadoff, Ira (Box 73)
        - Alienation from Nature (Box 73)
        - Last Poem for the Breast (Box 73)
        - Poem to My Wife [aka Fidelity] (Box 73)
      - Sakamoto, Naomi (Box 73)
        - Monkey on My Back (Box 73)
      - Salinger, J. B. (Box 73)
        - The Collected Works of Clifford Irving (Box 73)
        - The Complete Works of Clifford Irving (Box 73)
      - Salinger, J.D. (Box 73)
        - A Salute to Whit Burnett, 1899-1972 (Box 73)
        - Photocopies of news stories (Box 73)
      - Sandblom, John (Box 73)
        - Lead (Box 73)
      - Sanders, Steve (Box 73)
        - Brother [aka Birthday] (Box 73)
      - Sandow, Star (Box 73)
        - We're on Our Way [aka Gliding on Silent Hinges] (Box 73)
      - Sarki, Michael T. (Box 73)
        - Poems (Box 73)
          - Affair [aka Dish] (Box 73)
          - After Harvest (Box 73)
          - Bad Sky (Box 73)
          - Blue Dirt (Box 73)
          - Full Eclipse of the Son (Box 73)
          - Glaring (Box 73)
          - The Main Dish (Box 73)
          - Portland (Box 73)
          - The Preacher (Box 73)
          - Tree [aka Deflection] (Box 73)
          - Tulip [aka Nipple] (Box 73)
        - Zimble Zamble Zumble (Box 73)
          - Tulip (Box 73)
          - Blue Dirt (Box 73)
          - Tree (Box 73)
          - The Preacher (Box 73)
          - Lake (Box 73)
          - Woodshed (Box 73)
          - Beast (Box 73)
          - Gorilla (Box 73)
          - Affair (Box 73)
          - Mother (Box 73)
          - St. Louis (Box 73)
          - Sault Saint Marie (Box 73)
          - Ausable (Box 73)
          - Long Beach (Box 73)
          - Crown Him (Box 73)
          - Embryo (Box 73)
          - Sinner (Box 73)
          - Gingerbread (Box 73)
          - Hotel (Box 73)
          - Muted Orange (Box 73)
          - Silver Creek (Box 73)
          - Plumbing (Box 73)
          - Flight (Box 73)
          - Appendages (Box 73)
          - Still Life (Box 73)
          - Subterfuge (Box 73)
          - All the Rivers Where Angels Sing (Box 73)
          - Cistern (Box 73)
          - Little Brother (Box 73)
          - Bird (Box 73)
          - Emily (Box 73)
          - Lender (Box 73)
          - Filament (Box 73)
          - Hilda (Box 73)
          - Why Wind Blows (Box 73)
          - The Darkness in the Lightness of Her Demitasse (Box 73)
          - Of Daphne Odora (Box 73)
          - Pavlo (Box 73)
          - Flower by Tightening (Box 73)
          - Napp's (Box 73)
          - A 1953 Comedy (Box 73)
          - Gordon-Gordon! (Box 73)
          - Of Posturing (Box 73)
          - Nest (Box 73)
          - Heat (Box 73)
          - Beneath the Giant Sycamore (Box 73)
          - Calories (Box 73)
          - Ruined Sleep (Box 73)
          - Dominocus (Box 73)
          - Setula Brouille' (Box 73)
          - The Importance of the Pyramids (Box 73)
          - Hungry (Box 73)
          - Closing on the Vine (Box 73)
          - In Her Tuttled Marsh (Box 73)
          - Powder (Box 73)
          - When Nothing Comes First (Box 73)
          - In Poulard, Tongue Is Spoken (Box 73)
          - Already Its Utterance Is Given (Box 73)
          - She Goes Forward (Box 73)
          - Pin Oak on Hazel (Box 73)
          - Brown Coat Draped over Chewed Cigars (Box 73)
          - Caught in the Broth, Gasping for Air (Box 73)
          - Her Hero Sleeps on Corners (Box 73)
          - Stranger to Himself (Box 73)
          - A Gale of Perfection (Box 73)
          - The Heart Pleads (Box 73)
          - Gianni's Testimone (Box 73)
          - For Gordon (Box 73)
          - Why, Then, Do We Vacuum This Carpet? (Box 73)
          - Long Robes Sublime (Box 73)
          - Gangrel's Lading (Box 73)
          - Fugleman's (Box 73)
          - The Largest Man Beneath This Bridge (Box 73)
          - Behind the Wooden Stairs (Box 73)
          - Raising the Phulkari (Box 73)
          - Once, a Fascicle (Box 73)
          - In a Garden of Comestibles (Box 73)
          - Kloof in the Propylaeum (Box 73)
          - Of Levigations and Cascarilla (Box 73)